Finding aid to Amnesty International's Country Dossiers, Europe, Albania to Estonia.
IDC Publishers
- Bulgaria, 9
  - General AI material / Background papers, E
    - Bulgaria: Where are the men of Dragash Voyvoda?, 1 June 2003; (EUR 15/005/03); E113 (Microfiche 349)
    - Bulgaria., 1 October 2003; Concerns in Europe and Central Asia January - June 2003.; (EUR 01/016/03); E114 (Microfiche 349)
    - Bulgaria: Public Appeal - Fakia social care home for children., 6 November 2003; (EUR 15/011/03); E115 (Microfiche 350)
    - Bulgaria: Europe and Central Asia: Concerns in Europe and Central Asia: July - December 2003., 1 May 2004; (EUR 01/01/04); E116 (Microfiche 374)
    - Bulgaria:, 1 September 2004; Europe and Central Asia: Summary of Amnesty International's Concerns in the Region January - June 2004.; (EUR 01/05/04); E117 (Microfiche 374)
    - Bulgaria:, 16 November 2004; Sudan: Arming the perpetrators of grave abuses in Darfur.; (AFR 54/139/04); E118 (Microfiche 374)
    - Children of Dzhurkovo denied life of dignity and respect., 18 November 2004; (EUR 15/02/04); E119 (Microfiche 374)
    - Bulgaria: Give the children of Dzhurkovo a chance to realize their dreams., 18 November 2004; (EUR 15/03/04); E120 (Microfiche 374)
    - Bulgaria: Failings in the provision of care: The fate of the men of Dragash Voyvoda., 17 February 2005; (EUR 15/002/2005); E121 (Microfiche 397-398)
    - Bulgaria., 1 September 2005; Europe and Central Asia: Summary of Amnesty International's Concerns in the Region: July - December 2004.; (EUR 01/002/2005); E122 (Microfiche 398)
    - Bulgaria and Romania: Amnesty International's Human Rights Concerns in the EU Accession Countries., 1 October 2005; (EUR 02/001/2005); E123 (Microfiche 398)
    - Bulgaria., 1 December 2005; Europe Central Asia: Summary of Amnesty International's Concerns in the Region: January - June 2005.; (EUR 01/012/2005); E124 (Microfiche 398)
- Croatia, 10
  - Annual Report entry, B
    - Croatia., 1 July 1993; Amnesty International Report 1993.; (POL 10/01/93); B1 (Microfiche 150)
    - Croatia., 7 July 1994; Amnesty International Report 1994.; (POL 10/02/94); B2 (Microfiche 168)
    - Croatia., 1 July 1995; Amnesty International Report 1995.; (POL 10/01/95); B3 (Microfiche 186)
    - Croatia., 6 July 1995; Amnesty International Report 1995 updates.; (POL 10/04/95); B4 (Microfiche 186)
    - Croatia., 18 June 1996; Amnesty International Report 1996.; (POL 10/02/96); B5 (Microfiche 207)
    - Croatia., 18 June 1997; Amnesty International Report 1997.; (POL 10/01/97); B6 (Microfiche 225)
    - Croatia., 17 June 1998; Amnesty International Report 1998.; (POL 10/01/98); B7 (Microfiche 244)
    - Croatia., 16 June 1999; Amnesty International Report 1999.; (POL 10/01/99); B8 (Microfiche 263)
    - Croatia., 14 June 2000; Amnesty International Report 2000.; (POL 10/01/00); B9 (Microfiche 285)
    - Croatia., 30 May 2001; Amnesty International Report 2001.; (POL 10/01/01); B10 (Microfiche 306)
    - Croatia., 28 May 2002; Amnesty International Report 2002.; (POL 10/01/02); B11 (Microfiche 326)
    - Croatia., 28 May 2003; Amnesty International Report 2003.; (POL 10/003/03); B12 (Microfiche 350)
    - Croatia., 26 May 2004; Amnesty International Report 2004.; (POL 10/04/04); B13 (Microfiche 374)
    - Croatia., 25 May 2005; Amnesty International Report 2005.; (POL 10/001/2005); B14 (Microfiche 398)
  - News releases, C
    - Croatia: Amnesty International calls for human rights monitoring and protection to be made a priority for new UN force., 6 April 1995; Amnesty International News Service 70/95.; (NWS 11/70/95); C1 (Microfiche 186)
    - Croatia: Amnesty seeks President Tudjman's assurances that refugees from Velika Kladusa are not forcibly returned., 17 August 1995; (EUR 64/04/95); C2 (Microfiche 186)
    - Croatia: Human rights violations in the Krajina., 29 September 1995; (EUR 64/08/95); C3 (Microfiche 186)
    - Croatia: Amnesty International condemns prosecution of Feral Tribune journalists in Croatia., 20 May 1996; (EUR 64/09/96); C4 (Microfiche 207)
    - Croatia: Amnesty International calls for justice for Sinisa Glavasevic and other victims of unlawful execution in Vukovar., 14 March 1997; (EUR 64/01/97); C5 (Microfiche 225)
    - Croatia: Too soon to hail success in Eastern Slavonia., 15 January 1998; (EUR 64/01/98); C6 (Microfiche 244)
    - Refugees from Former Yugoslavia - send the right message for Kosovo: learn from and remedy the policy failures over Bosnia and Croatia''., 25 June 1998; (EUR 05/01/98); C7 (Microfiche 244)
    - Croatia: Three years since operations Flash and Storm - three years of justice and dignity denied., 4 August 1998; (EUR 64/05/98); C8 (Microfiche 244)
    - Croatia: Minister of the Interior should answer on specific cases., 5 August 1998; (EUR 64/06/98); C9 (Microfiche 244)
    - Croatia: Statistics and laws alone will not end torture and ill-treatment., 9 November 1998; (EUR 64/09/98); C10 (Microfiche 244)
    - Former Yugoslavia: AI appeals to Government representatives to finally resolve the issue of missing persons., 24 March 1999; (EUR 05/01/99); C11 (Microfiche 263)
    - Croatia: War crimes prosecutions should not be obstructed., 13 February 2001; (EUR 64/01/01); C12 (Microfiche 306)
    - Croatia/Federal Republic of Yugoslavia: Vukovar - ten years of impunity for massive human rights violations., 16 November 2001; (EUR 05/02/01); C13 (Microfiche 306)
    - Croatia: Victims and witnesses in war crimes trials must be adequately protected., 20 June 2002; (EUR 64/02/02); C14 (Microfiche 326)
    - Croatia: Implement recommendations to prevent torture., 28 May 2004; (EUR 64/02/04); C15 (Microfiche 374)
    - Croatia: Rights of children must be respected., 5 October 2004; (EUR 64/04/04); C16 (Microfiche 374)
    - Croatia: Impunity for war crimes and crimes against humanity must end., 13 December 2004; (EUR 64/06/04); C17 (Microfiche 374)
    - Croatia: Impunity for war crimes must end., 16 March 2005; (EUR 64/001/2005); C18 (Microfiche 398)
    - Croatia: Operation Storm'' - still no justice ten years on., 4 August 2005; (EUR 64/002/2005); C19 (Microfiche 398)
    - Croatia: European Court of Human Rights to consider important case for refugee returns., 14 September 2005; (EUR 64/003/2005); C20 (Microfiche 398)
    - Croatia: Gotovina to go to The Hague., 8 December 2005; (EUR 64/006/2005); C21 (Microfiche 398)
  - Newsletter entries, D
    - Croatia: Tonci Majic., 1 August 1994; AI Newsletter August 1994.; (NWS 21/08/94) (Focus: Freedom's front line) (includes photograph); D1 (Microfiche 168)
    - Croatia: Disappeared'' must not be forgotten (includes photograph)., 1 October 1995; Amnesty International Newsletter October 1995.; (NWS 21/10/95); D2 (Microfiche 186)
  - General AI material / Background papers, E
    - Croatia: ratifications., 12/1992; Amnesty International's Concerns in Europe May 1992 - October 1992.; (EUR 01/04/92); E1 (Microfiche 134)
    - Croatia: Velimir Zecevic, retired judge., 1 March 1993; (EUR 64/01/93); E2 (Microfiche 150)
    - Croatia: Extrajudicial executions; deaths in custody alleged to result from torture and ill-treatment; fair trial concerns., 1 June 1993; Concerns in Europe November 1992 - April 1993.; (EUR 01/01/93); E3 (Microfiche 151)
    - Croatia: Europe must open its doors to take more Bosnian refugees from Croatia where they are at increasing risk., 15 June 1993; Weekly Update Service 63/93.; (NWS 11/63/93); E4 (Microfiche 151)
    - Croatia., 1 September 1993; Refugee protection at risk: Amnesty International's recommendations to the 44th session of the Executive Committee of UNHCR.; (POL 33/06/93); E5 (Microfiche 151)
    - Croatia., 1 October 1993; Political killings and disappearances'': medicolegal aspects.; (ACT 33/36/93); E6 (Microfiche 151)
    - Medical letter writing action: Croatia: Doctor charged with service in an enemy army: Jadrana Funduk., 19 October 1993; (EUR 64/02/93); E7 (Microfiche 151)
    - Follow up to medical letter-writing action (see EUR 64/02/93) - Croatia: Dr Jadrana Funduk., 22 November 1993; (EUR 64/03/93); E8 (Microfiche 151)
    - Croatia: Freedom of expression; forcible return of Muslim asylum-seekers from Bosnia-Herzegovina., 1 January 1994; Concerns in Europe May - October 1993.; (EUR 01/01/94); E9 (Microfiche 168)
    - Croatia: Conscientious objection., 1 June 1994; Concerns in Europe November 1993 - April 1994.; (EUR 01/02/94); E10 (Microfiche 168)
    - Croatia: Disappearance'' of Rasim Kahrimanovic., 17 June 1994; (EUR 64/02/94); E11 (Microfiche 168)
    - Croatia: Beating of demonstrators during evictions from former Yugoslav Army apartments., 1 February 1995; Concerns in Europe May-December 1994.; (EUR 01/01/95); E12 (Microfiche 186)
    - Croatia: Concerns arising from the Croatian military action in Western Slavonia; concerns in the Croatian Serb-controlled areas., 1 September 1995; Concerns in Europe January-June 1995.; (EUR 01/02/95); E13 (Microfiche 186)
    - Croatia: Nenad Dujikovic and Dragan Mirkovic - Feared disappearance''., 21 September 1995; (EUR 64/06/95); E14 (Microfiche 186)
    - Croatia: Violent evictions by uniformed personnel: D.P. and S.P., Vjekoslav and Nikolina Vukman, and Zdenka Bibernik., 21 November 1995; (EUR 64/12/95); E15 (Microfiche 186)
    - Croatia: Possible prisoner of conscience: Bozidar Balenovic., 11 January 1996; (EUR 64/01/96); E16 (Microfiche 207)
    - Croatia: Ill-treatment including rape in the Zuzija apartment., 1 February 1996; (EUR 64/03/96); E17 (Microfiche 207)
    - Croatia., 1 March 1996; Concerns in Europe July - December 1995.; (EUR 01/01/96); E18 (Microfiche 207)
    - Croatia: Continued violence used by uniformed personnel in connection with evictions., 1 April 1996; (EUR 64/08/96); E19 (Microfiche 207)
    - Croatia., 1 August 1996; Concerns in Europe January - June 1996.; (EUR 01/02/96); E20 (Microfiche 207)
    - Croatia., 1 March 1997; Concerns in Europe July - December 1996.; (EUR 01/01/97); E21 (Microfiche 226)
    - Croatia., 19 March 1997; Bosnia-Herzegovina: Who's living in my house?'': Obstacles to the safe return of refugees and displaced people.; (EUR 63/01/97); E22 (Microfiche 226)
    - Croatia., 15 April 1997; Out of the margins: the right to conscientious objection to military service in Europe.; (EUR 01/02/97); E23 (Microfiche 226)
    - Human rights monitoring in Croatia: Amnesty International's recommendations to strengthen the new OSCE mandate., 13 June 1997; (EUR 64/03/97); E24 (Microfiche 226)
    - Croatia: Attacks in the Hrvatska Kostajnica area., 1 August 1997; (EUR 64/05/97); E25 (Microfiche 226)
    - Croatia: Attacks on Croatian Serbs around Kostajnica., 1 September 1997; Concerns in Europe January - June 1997.; (EUR 01/06/97); E26 (Microfiche 226)
    - Croatia: Mirjana Galo, attacked for human rights work., 1 October 1997; Defend the defenders of the Universal Declaration of Human Rights.; (ACT 30/04/97); E27 (Microfiche 226)
    - Croatia: Restrictions on freedom of expression., 1 November 1997; AI Concerns in Europe: July-October 1997 Supplement.; (EUR 01/07/97); E28 (Microfiche 226)
    - Croatia: Restrictions on freedom of expression; continuing harassment of Croatian Serbs; release of Bosnian Serb prisoners; arrest of suspects follow confessions to war crimes., 1 February 1998; Concerns in Europe, July - December 1997.; (EUR 01/01/98); E29 (Microfiche 244)
    - Croatia: Ill-treatment and rape of women during eviction., 1 March 1998; Why are we still waiting?'' The struggle for women's human rights.; (ACT 30/04/98); E30 (Microfiche 244)
    - Croatia: Attacks in the Hrvatska Kostajnica area - the effects of impunity., 1 July 1998; (EUR 64/02/98); E31 (Microfiche 244)
    - Croatia: Impunity for killings after Storm., 1 August 1998; (EUR 64/04/98); E32 (Microfiche 244-245)
    - Croatia: Dignity finally brought to some victims from Vukovar; trials of Croatian Serbs; Croatian Serbs' exile perpetuated by violence and other obstacles; potential prisoners of conscience; police ill-treatment of Zagreb youth results in hospitalizations., 1 September 1998; Concerns in Europe January-June 1998.; (EUR 01/02/98); E33 (Microfiche 245)
    - Croatia: Mirko Graorac: Shortchanging justice - war crimes trials in former Yugoslavia., 1 December 1998; (EUR 64/10/98); E34 (Microfiche 245)
    - Croatia: Impunity following the death in custody of tefik Mujkic., 1 February 1999; (EUR 64/01/99); E35 (Microfiche 263)
    - Croatia., 1 April 1999; Concerns in Europe July-December 1998.; (EUR 01/01/99); E36 (Microfiche 263)
    - Croatia: Update on government reactions to reports of human rights abuses committed after Operation Storm., 1 August 1999; Concerns in Europe January - June 1999.; (EUR 01/02/99); E37 (Microfiche 263)
    - Croatia: Fear for safety: violent attacks against Serbs in eastern Slavonia., 23 August 1999; (EUR 64/04/99); E38 (Microfiche 263)
    - Croatia: Shortchanging justice: The 'Sodolovci' group., 1 December 1999; (EUR 64/06/99); E39 (Microfiche 263)
    - Croatia., 1 March 2000; Europe: Concerns in Europe July-December 1999.; (EUR 01/01/00); E40 (Microfiche 285)
    - Croatia., 21 August 2000; Europe: Concerns in Europe: January - June 2000.; (EUR 01/03/00); E41 (Microfiche 285)
    - Croatia: Operation Flash and Storm''., 6 November 2000; Failures at Fifty: Impunity for torture and ill-treatment in Europe on the 50th anniversary of the European Convention on Human Rights.; (EUR 01/04/00); E42 (Microfiche 285)
    - Croatia., 1 March 2001; Concerns in Europe July-December 2000.; (EUR 01/01/01); E43 (Microfiche 306)
    - Croatia., 1 September 2001; Concerns in Europe January - June 2001.; (EUR 01/03/01); E44 (Microfiche 306)
    - Croatia., 30 May 2002; Concerns in Europe Bulletin: July - December 2001.; (EUR 01/02/02); E45 (Microfiche 326)
    - Croatia., 1 September 2002; Concerns in Europe January - June 2002.; (EUR 01/07/02); E46 (Microfiche 326)
    - Croatia., 1 October 2003; Concerns in Europe and Central Asia January - June 2003.; (EUR 01/016/03); E47 (Microfiche 350)
    - Croatia: Europe and Central Asia: Concerns in Europe and Central Asia: July - December 2003., 1 May 2004; (EUR 01/01/04); E48 (Microfiche 374)
    - Croatia: Briefing to the United Nations Committee against Torture., 28 May 2004; (EUR 64/01/04); E49 (Microfiche 374)
    - Croatia:, 1 September 2004; Europe and Central Asia: Summary of Amnesty International's Concerns in the Region January - June 2004.; (EUR 01/05/04); E50 (Microfiche 374)
    - Croatia: Briefing to the United Nations Committee on the Rights of the Child: 37th Session, September 2004., 5 October 2004; (EUR 64/03/04); E51 (Microfiche 374-375)
    - Croatia: A shadow on Croatia's future: Continuing impunity for war crimes and crimes against humanity., 13 December 2004; (EUR 64/05/04); E52 (Microfiche 375)
    - Croatia: 10. Enlargement and neighbourhood policy., 1 June 2005; Delivering on human rights - Amnesty International's ten-point program for the UK Presidency of the European Union.; (IOR 61/017/2005); E53 (Microfiche 398)
    - Amnesty International's concerns on the implementation of the completion strategy'' of the International Criminal Tribunal for the former Yugoslavia., 6 June 2005; (EUR 05/001/2005); E54 (Microfiche 398)
    - Croatia., 1 September 2005; Europe and Central Asia: Summary of Amnesty International's Concerns in the Region: July - December 2004.; (EUR 01/002/2005); E55 (Microfiche 398)
    - Croatia: The right to education of minorities., 1 September 2005; Human rights for human dignity: A primer on economic, social and cultural rights.; (POL 34/009/2005); E56 (Microfiche 398)
    - Croatia., 1 December 2005; Europe Central Asia: Summary of Amnesty International's Concerns in the Region: January - June 2005.; (EUR 01/012/2005); E57 (Microfiche 398)
- Cyprus, 11
  - Publications, A
    - Cyprus., 1989; Country survey section of When the State Kills ...'' The Death Penalty v. Human Rights.; (ACT 51/07/89); A1 (Microfiche 97)
  - Annual Report entry, B
    - Amnesty International report 1980., B1 (Microfiche 22)
    - Amnesty International report 1985., B2 (Microfiche 57)
    - Amnesty International report 1986., B3 (Microfiche 66)
    - Cyprus., 1990; Amnesty International report 1990.; (POL 10/03/90); B4 (Microfiche 110)
    - Cyprus., 1991; Amnesty International Report 1991.; (POL 10/01/91); B5 (Microfiche 119)
    - Cyprus., 9/7/1992; Amnesty International Report 1992.; (POL 10/01/92); B6 (Microfiche 134)
    - Cyprus., 1 July 1993; Amnesty International Report 1993.; (POL 10/01/93); B7 (Microfiche 151)
    - Cyprus., 7 July 1994; Amnesty International Report 1994.; (POL 10/02/94); B8 (Microfiche 168)
    - Cyprus., 1 July 1995; Amnesty International Report 1995.; (POL 10/01/95); B9 (Microfiche 186)
    - Cyprus., 18 June 1996; Amnesty International Report 1996.; (POL 10/02/96); B10 (Microfiche 207)
    - Cyprus., 18 June 1997; Amnesty International Report 1997.; (POL 10/01/97); B11 (Microfiche 226)
    - Cyprus., 16 June 1999; Amnesty International Report 1999.; (POL 10/01/99); B12 (Microfiche 263)
    - Cyprus., 25 May 2005; Amnesty International Report 2005.; (POL 10/001/2005); B13 (Microfiche 398)
  - News releases, C
    - Advice to editors: Cyprus: Amnesty International says new law on conscientious objection not enough., 4/10/1990; (EUR 17/04/90); C1 (Microfiche 110)
    - Advice to editors: Cyprus: Amnesty International condemns jailing of conscientious objector., 12/3/1992; (EUR 17/01/92); C2 (Microfiche 134)
    - Cyprus: Imprisonment of conscientious objectors to military service continues., 22 April 1994; AI News Service 81/94.; (NWS 11/81/94); C3 (Microfiche 168)
    - Cyprus: Amnesty International condemns killings of Greek Cypriots and urges investigation., 15 August 1996; (EUR 17/02/96); C4 (Microfiche 207)
    - Cyprus: Amnesty International calls on House of Representatives to decriminalize consensual sex between adult males in private., 19 May 1997; (EUR 17/01/97); C5 (Microfiche 226)
    - Cyprus: Parliament should decriminalise consensual sex between adult males in private., 20 May 1998; (EUR 17/01/98); C6 (Microfiche 245)
    - Cyprus: Amnesty International calls for amendments to legislation on homosexuality., 18 June 1998; (EUR 17/02/98); C7 (Microfiche 245)
    - Cyprus threatens to breach the United Nations Refugee Convention., 23 July 1998; (EUR 17/03/98); C8 (Microfiche 245)
    - Cyprus: Conscientious objector status must be amended., 7 November 2002; (EUR 17/01/02); C9 (Microfiche 326)
  - Newsletter entries, D
    - Panayiotis Spetsiotis (appeal case)., 10/1985; D1 (Microfiche 57)
    - Cyprus: Panayiotis Spetsiotis (Prisoners of the Month 1985)., 8/1986; D2 (Microfiche 66)
    - Human rights violations in Europe: Cyprus., 8/1991; Amnesty International Newsletter, August 1991 (Focus on Europe).; D3 (Microfiche 119)
    - Cyprus., 1 January 1993; Amnesty International Newsletter January 1993 (Focus on religious victims of human rights violations).; D4 (Microfiche 151)
    - Northern Cyprus: Salih Askerogul, a conscientious objector and prisoner of conscience, sentenced to three years and three months (includes photograph)., 1 February 1994; AI Newsletter February 1994.; (NWS 21/02/94) (Worldwide appeals); D5 (Microfiche 168)
    - Cyprus: Iosif Kosta Kourides, conscientious objector and prisoner of conscience (Worldwide appeals - includes photograph)., 1 July 1995; Amnesty International Newsletter July 1995.; (NWS 21/07/95); D6 (Microfiche 186)
  - General AI material / Background papers, E
    - The death penalty in Western Europe. (Extract), 15/6/1984; (EUR 01/01/84); E1 (Microfiche 48)
    - The imprisonment of conscientious objectors to military service. (Extract), 26/3/1985; (POL 31/01/85); E2 (Microfiche 57)
    - Cyprus., 28/5/1986; The death penalty in Western Europe.; (EUR 03/02/86); E3 (Microfiche 66)
    - Cyprus: The death penalty., 4/1987; Amnesty International concerns in Western Europe (October 1986 - March 1987).; (EUR 03/01/87); E4 (Microfiche 77)
    - Cyprus., 8/1987; The death penalty in Western Europe (Revised Edition August 1987).; (EUR 03/02/87); E5 (Microfiche 77)
    - Cyprus., 2/1988; Conscientious objection to military service.; (POL 31/01/88); E6 (Microfiche 87)
    - Concerns in W. Europe., 03/01/1989; E7 (Microfiche 97)
    - Cyprus: 1. Conscientious objection. 2. Missing persons - further developments. In: Amnesty International concerns in Western Europe, March - September 1989., 11/1989; (EUR 03/02/89); E8 (Microfiche 97)
    - Missing persons in Cyprus: Amnesty International's actions, 1974-1989., 8/1989; (EUR 17/02/89); E9 (Microfiche 97)
    - Cyprus: Yannis Parpas., 24/10/1989; (EUR 17/03/89); E10 (Microfiche 97)
    - Cyprus: Conscientious objection., 5/1990; Amnesty International concerns in Western Europe, October 1989 - April 1990.; (EUR 03/01/90); E11 (Microfiche 110)
    - Cyprus: Amnesty International says new law on conscientious objection not enough., 17/9/1990; Weekly Update Service 37/90.; (NWS 11/37/90); E12 (Microfiche 110)
    - Cyprus: Update to proposed law on conscientious objection., 4/10/1990; Weekly Update Service 39/90.; (NWS 11/39/90); E13 (Microfiche 110)
    - Cyprus., 11/1990; Western Europe: concerns May - October 1990.; (EUR 03/02/90); E14 (Microfiche 110)
    - Cyprus: Georgios Anastasi Petrou., 18/1/1990; (EUR 17/01/90); E15 (Microfiche 110)
    - Cyprus: Christakis Jonathan Christoforou., 11/3/1990; (EUR 17/02/90); E16 (Microfiche 110)
    - Cyprus: Antonis Georgiou Antoniadis., 11/3/1990; (EUR 17/03/90); E17 (Microfiche 110)
    - Cyprus., 1/1991; Conscientious objection to military service.; (POL 31/01/91); E18 (Microfiche 119)
    - Cyprus: Conscientious objection to military service., 6/1991; Concerns in Europe November 1990 - April 1991.; (EUR 01/01/91); E19 (Microfiche 119)
    - Cyprus: Conscientious objection to military service; torture allegations., 11/1991; Concerns in Europe May - October 1991.; (EUR 01/02/91); E20 (Microfiche 119)
    - Cyprus: ratifications., 11/1991; Concerns in Europe May - October 1991.; (EUR 01/02/91); E21 (Microfiche 119)
    - Cyprus: Government moves towards recognizing conscientious objection., 18/12/1991; Weekly Update Service 48/91.; (NWS 11/48/91); E22 (Microfiche 119)
    - Adoption network for conscientious objectors in Western Europe: Cyprus 10/91: Yiannakis Charalampous Galatis., 29/5/1991; (EUR 17/02/91); E23 (Microfiche 119)
    - Adoption network for conscientious objectors in Western Europe: Cyprus: Marios Andrea Christofi., 29/5/1991; (EUR 17/03/91); E24 (Microfiche 119)
    - Adoption network for conscientious objectors in Western Europe: Cyprus 12/91: Theocharis Theocle Theocharidis., 18/6/1991; (EUR 17/04/91); E25 (Microfiche 119)
    - Adoption network for conscientious objectors in Western Europe: Cyprus 13/91: Omiros Konstantinou., 10/7/1991; (EUR 17/05/91); E26 (Microfiche 119)
    - ANCOWE 14/91: Cyprus: Linos Charalambous., 10/7/1991; (EUR 17/06/91); E27 (Microfiche 119)
    - Adoption network for conscientious objectors in Western Europe: Cyprus 15/91: Antonis Orthodoxou., 10/7/1991; (EUR 17/07/91); E28 (Microfiche 119)
    - Adoption network for conscientious objectors in Western Europe: Cyprus Panayiotis Leonida Georgalidis., 16/10/1991; (EUR 17/10/91); E29 (Microfiche 119)
    - ANCOWE: Cyprus 17/91: Zinona Andrea Zinonos., 4/11/1991; (EUR 17/11/91); E30 (Microfiche 119)
    - Cyprus: Abolitionist for all but exceptional crimes., 2/1992; Europe: Moving towards complete abolition of the death penalty.; (EUR 01/01/92); E31 (Microfiche 134)
    - Cyprus: Amnesty International condemns jailing of conscientious objector (Sideris Georgiou Isidorou)., 12/3/1992; Weekly Update Service 10/92.; (NWS 11/10/92); E32 (Microfiche 134)